(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 1,
"subtitles": 2
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
テレパシーより伝えたい歌声を
A singing voice I want to convey more than telepathy...
重ね合わせて
...overlapping each other...
宇宙の果てまで
...to the ends of the universe.
カラフルな夢が降り注ぐこの空
In this sky where colorful dreams pour down,
未来も過去も抱きしめよう
let's embrace both the future and the past.
きっと星が手をつないで
Surely the stars will hold hands...
優しい光で
...with a gentle light...
溢れるように
...so that it overflows.
ここから始まる
Starting from here...
アドベンチャー
...is an adventure.
せーの！
One, two!
アドベンチャー！そらあずびーむ！
Adventure! SorAZ Beam!
せーの！で深呼吸
One, two! Take a deep breath.
始まってく ここから Ready Go!
It's starting from here, Ready Go!
大気圏突き抜けて
Piercing through the atmosphere...
揺れぬ想い歌声も
...even my unwavering feelings and singing voice...
意識を飛び越えて
...jump past consciousness...
響く キラキラ
...and echo, sparkling.
天使の境地
The realm of an angel,
漂い巡り合い
drifting and coming across each other.
瞬間 ドキする
In an instant, my heart thumps,
奇跡的で
it's miraculous.
BPM 高まって
BPM is rising,
くるくる回る みんな
everyone is spinning around...
まるでミラーボール
...just like a mirror ball.
私たちの夢のファーストプレス
The first press of our dreams...
思い切り遊ぼう
...let's play with all our might.
SorAZ 空を駆けて振り切っちゃって Go!
SorAZ, run through the sky, leave it all behind, and Go!
化学反応で生み出す光
The light created by a chemical reaction,
今ここで繋がった
connected right here and now.
照らして 照らし合って
Shine, and shine on each other,
せーので 頷いて
one, two, and nod.
始まってく ワンダー レリゴー！
It's starting, wonder, let it go!
ときめき 増幅して
Amplifying the excitement...
開くは 新時代
...opening up is a new era.
可能性 その身を投げ出して
Possibilities, throw yourself into them.
時代の エーテルに
Into the ether of the era...
ドキドキ 連動する
...my heart thumps in sync.
孤高の 一等星
A solitary first-magnitude star...
運命の シンコペーション
A syncopation of fate,
星屑の Runaway
a runaway of stardust...
投げる キラピカ
...throwing sparkles.
虹の彼方光る
Shining beyond the rainbow...
フューチャーサイン キャッチして
...catch the future sign.
アイとユー 奏でるのは ミラクルデイ
What I and You play is a miracle day.
以心伝心で まるでテレパシー
Like mind-to-mind communication, it's just like telepathy.
今という 瞬間を
This moment called "now"...
感じて 感じ合って
...feel it, feel each other.
せーの！で深呼吸
One, two! Take a deep breath.
見たことないワンダー 君と
A wonder I've never seen, with you.
研ぎ澄ます 想いが作る世界
A world created by sharpened thoughts.
ここにある ここにいるよ 歌を
It's here, I'm here, sing a song...
歌えば 一つになれる
...if you sing, we can become one.
もっとなれるよ 自由に
We can become even more free.
ようこそ ここはバイアスのない 二人のエキスポ
Welcome, this is our unbiased expo.
ギャラクシースペース！
Galaxy Space!
私たちの夢のファーストプレス
The first press of our dreams...
思い切り遊ぼう
...let's play with all our might.
SorAZ 空を駆けて振り切っちゃって Go!
SorAZ, run through the sky, leave it all behind, and Go!
化学反応で生み出す光
The light created by a chemical reaction,
今ここで繋がった
connected right here and now.
照らして 照らし合って
Shine, and shine on each other,
せーので 深呼吸
one, two, take a deep breath.
どこまでも 行こうよ
Let's go everywhere.
せーので 頷いて
One, two, and nod.
始まってく ワンダー レリゴー！
It's starting, wonder, let it go!
完璧な メジャーステップ
A perfect major step,
星振る街で 過ごす タイム イェーイ！
spending time in the star-falling town, yeah!
展示未到のときめき知りたい人？
Who wants to know an unprecedented thrill?
いっせーの！で言っちゃいな！
Say it on the count of three!
今だっていいじゃない！
Right now is fine, too!
いっせーの！で言っちゃいな！
Say it on the count of three!
今だっていいじゃない！
Right now is fine, too!
旧法を徒にする奴ぶっちゃいたい人？
Who wants to blast those who follow the old rules?
それって君じゃない！
Isn't that you?
今日は言っちゃいいじゃない！
You can say it today!
M・E・G・A・M・E　そりゃマブの目
M-E-G-A-M-E, those are the real eyes.
ピンチこそ人生の醍醐味です
Pinches are the real thrill of life.
いっせーので出しちゃえ！
Let's put it out on the count of three!
飛んでハート出しちゃえ！
Jump and let your heart out!
この際もうはや死角はない
At this point, there are no blind spots left.
動かなかった足を今踏み出したいと思える
I feel like I want to take a step with my feet that wouldn't move.
一人ではできなかった事よやっちゃお
Let's do the things I couldn't do alone.
いっちゃうよ！
Here we go!
いっせーのせ！
On the count of three!
一個一個 ぶっ飛んでいくぞ
One by one, we're gonna blast off!
君の体温上昇期はまだまだ
Your body temperature is still rising.
でも一歩一歩って進んでいくぞ
But we're moving forward step by step.
これが我らの第一歩
This is our first step.
しかと見ておいてくださいな
Please make sure to watch closely.
転んだり迷ったりお気になさらず
Don't worry about falling or getting lost.
もうちょっと突き抜けてくださいませ
Please break through a little more.
努力も尖る時に減速なんてな事ございません
There's no slowing down when your efforts are peaking.
渾身的なメジャービジョン
A wholehearted major vision.
星降るでしょうハッピーイェイ
Stars will fall, happy yay!
もしや今とてもいい感じ？
Are things feeling great right now?
もっとギア上げちゃっていい感じ？
Is it okay to shift up a gear?
今日という日は一回だけ
Today only happens once.
だから目一杯声出してみよう Let's go, say!
So let's shout as loud as we can. Let's go, say!
オー・オー　世界一、アズキ！
Oh oh! The best in the world, AZKi!
オー・オー　いいよ、もっと、もう一回！
Oh oh! That's it, more, one more time!
オー・オー　宇宙一、楽しく！
Oh oh! The most fun in the universe!
オー・オー　あー、めっちゃ最高！
Oh oh! Ah, this is the best!
過去も今だって未来に
The past and even the present are for the future.
今は期待と足しちゃってみる
I'll try adding my expectations to the now.
君がいたから見れた景色
The scenery I saw because you were there.
やっちゃうよ！いっちゃうよ！
Let's do it! Let's go!
いっせーのせ！
On the count of three!
一个一个って突っ込んだものの
I plunged in one by one, but...
とどまってるでっかい世界にクラクラ
Dizzy in this massive world where I'm stuck.
でも一歩一歩を大事にするぞ
But I'll cherish every single step.
それが我らの第一歩
That is our first step.
いっせーのでぶっ飛んでいくぞ
Let's blast off on the count of three!
君の体温上昇期はもうすぐ
Your body temperature's rising phase is coming soon.
この一歩一歩を楽しんでいくぞ
We're going to enjoy these steps one by one.
それじゃみんなで第一歩
So now, everyone, our first step!
しかと見ておいてくださいな
Please make sure to watch closely.
転んだり迷ったりお気になさらず
Don't worry about falling or getting lost.
もうちょっと突き抜けてくださいませ
Please break through a little more.
努力も尖る時に減速なんてな事ございません
There's no slowing down when your efforts are peaking.
ずっと見ていてくださいな
Please keep watching us forever.
笑ってる弾んでる未来が見えませ
Show us a laughing, bouncing future.
テンポも心もご覧くださいませ
Please see our tempo and our hearts.
ときそらAZKiに退屈なんてな事ございません
There's no such thing as boredom with Tokino Sora and AZKi.
渾身的なメジャービジョン
A wholehearted major vision.
星降るでしょうハッピーイェイ
Stars will fall, happy yay!
展示未到のときめき知りたい人？
Who wants to know an unprecedented thrill?
いっせーの！で言っちゃいな！
Say it on the count of three!
今だっていいじゃない！
Right now is fine, too!
いっせーの！で言っちゃいな！
Say it on the count of three!
今だっていいじゃない！
Right now is fine, too!
旧法を徒にする奴ぶっちゃいたい人？
Who wants to blast those who follow the old rules?
それって君じゃない！
Isn't that you?
今日は言っちゃいいじゃない！
You can say it today!
M・E・G・A・M・E　そりゃマブの目
M-E-G-A-M-E, those are the real eyes.
ピンチこそ人生の醍醐味です
Pinches are the real thrill of life.
いっせーので出しちゃえ！
Let's put it out on the count of three!
飛んでハート出しちゃえ！
Jump and let your heart out!
この際もうはや死角はない
At this point, there are no blind spots left.
動かなかった足を今踏み出したいと思える
I feel like I want to take a step with my feet that wouldn't move.
一人ではできなかった事よやっちゃお
Let's do the things I couldn't do alone.
いっちゃうよ！
Here we go!
いっせーのせ！
On the count of three!
一個一個 ぶっ飛んでいくぞ
One by one, we're gonna blast off!
君の体温上昇期はまだまだ
Your body temperature is still rising.
でも一歩一歩って進んでいくぞ
But we're moving forward step by step.
これが我らの第一歩
This is our first step.
しかと見ておいてくださいな
Please make sure to watch closely.
転んだり迷ったりお気になさらず
Don't worry about falling or getting lost.
もうちょっと突き抜けてくださいませ
Please break through a little more.
努力も尖る時に減速なんてな事ございません
There's no slowing down when your efforts are peaking.
渾身的なメジャービジョン
A wholehearted major vision.
星降るでしょうハッピーイェイ
Stars will fall, happy yay!
もしや今とてもいい感じ？
Are things feeling great right now?
もっとギア上げちゃっていい感じ？
Is it okay to shift up a gear?
今日という日は一回だけ
Today only happens once.
だから目一杯声出してみよう Let's go, say!
So let's shout as loud as we can. Let's go, say!
オー・オー　世界一、アズキ！
Oh oh! The best in the world, AZKi!
オー・オー　いいよ、もっと、もう一回！
Oh oh! That's it, more, one more time!
オー・オー　宇宙一、楽しく！
Oh oh! The most fun in the universe!
オー・オー　あー、めっちゃ最高！
Oh oh! Ah, this is the best!
過去も今だって未来に
The past and even the present are for the future.
今は期待と足しちゃってみる
I'll try adding my expectations to the now.
君がいたから見れた景色
The scenery I saw because you were there.
やっちゃうよ！いっちゃうよ！
Let's do it! Let's go!
いっせーのせ！
On the count of three!
一个一个って突っ込んだものの
I plunged in one by one, but...
とどまってるでっかい世界にクラクラ
Dizzy in this massive world where I'm stuck.
でも一歩一歩を大事にするぞ
But I'll cherish every single step.
それが我らの第一歩
That is our first step.
いっせーのでぶっ飛んでいくぞ
Let's blast off on the count of three!
君の体温上昇期はもうすぐ
Your body temperature's rising phase is coming soon.
この一歩一歩を楽しんでいくぞ
We're going to enjoy these steps one by one.
差し入れを贈ってくださったそらとも・開拓者の皆様、本当にありがとうございます！
To all the Soratomo and Pioneers who sent us gifts, thank you so much!
AZKi メジャーデビューEP「3枚目の地図」好評配信中！
AZKi's Major Debut EP "Sanmaime no Chizu" is now available on streaming platforms!
AZKi 「トウキョウ・シャンディ・ランデヴ」(Cover) 配信中！
AZKi's cover of "Tokyo Shandy Rendezvous" is now available on streaming platforms!
AZKi 「Sincerely」(Cover) 配信中！
AZKi's cover of "Sincerely" is now available on streaming platforms!
ときのそら 2024年3月6日(水) Release Mini Album「STAR STAR☆T」リリース決定！
Tokino Sora's Mini Album "STAR STAR☆T" will be released on Wednesday, March 6, 2024!
ときのそら 歌ってみた「可愛くてごめん」配信中！
Tokino Sora's cover of "Kawaikute Gomen" is now available on streaming platforms!
SorAZ メジャーデビューアルバム「Futurity Step」好評配信中！
SorAZ's Major Debut Album "Futurity Step" is now available on streaming platforms!
Major Debut Live「First Gravity」CD物販限定特典
Major Debut Live "First Gravity" CD Sales Limited Bonus
バイバイ・テクノロジー
Bye-bye technology
こんな思考もホコリ出して
Dumping out all these thoughts
空っぽみたいに
As if I'm empty
愛し合いたいだけなのに
Even though I just want us to love each other
くらっときた瞬間 私のなかで
The moment I felt dizzy, inside of me
きっと宇宙が始まったんだ
Surely the universe had begun
なぜか惹き付けられるよう だけど
It's like I'm being drawn in for some reason, but
瞬きするたびに見失ってばかりで
I keep losing sight every time I blink
予測ができない ナチュラル・アモルファス
Unpredictable natural amorphous
私のレンズじゃ 捉えられないけれど
Even though I can't capture it with my lens
惑わすあなたと出会いたいな
I want to meet you who confuses me
迷わず行けたら 遠くの星は
If I could go without hesitation, the distant stars
いつでも眩しくて 私を導いて
Would always be dazzling, guiding me
微笑んでるの
And smiling
もっと近づきたくて
I want to get closer
あなたを知りたくて
I want to know you
星影に私 触れちゃったみたい
It's like I've touched the starlight
探して やっと見つけて
Searching, finally found you
どうして こんなに接近しても
Why, even when I get this close
まだ重力反転
Is gravity still reversed?
駆け引き 上手ね 無邪気なプラネット
You're good at bargaining, you innocent planet
わがままで願うばかりじゃ
If I only keep wishing selfishly
きっと離れちゃうんだね いつか
We'll surely drift apart someday
私を惑わす星よ
Oh, star that confuses me
惑わすあなたと出会いたいな
I want to meet you who confuses me
迷わず行けたら
If I could go without hesitation
遠くの星は
The distant stars
いつでも眩しくて 私を導いて
Would always be dazzling, guiding me
微笑んで
Smiling
惑わすあなたを攫いたいな
I want to snatch you away who confuses me
迷わず言えたら
If I could say it without hesitation
遠くの星は
The distant stars
いつでも優しくて 私は導かれ
Would always be kind, and I'd be guided
微笑んでるの
Smiling
ずっと近づきたくて
I want to get closer forever
あなたを知りたくて
I want to know you
星影に私 触れちゃったみたい
It's like I've touched the starlight
エルタマ 差し入れ企画 参加者様一覧
Eltama Gift Project Participant List
差し入れを贈ってくださったそらまめの皆様、本当にありがとうございます！
To all the Soramame who sent gifts, thank you very much!
本日は、SorAZ Major Debut Live『First Gravity』
Thank you very much for coming to the
at CLUB CITTA'にご来場、ご来場いただきまして、誠にありがとうございます。
SorAZ Major Debut Live 'First Gravity' at CLUB CITTA' today.
開演に先立ちまして、そらまめの皆様にお願いしたいことをお伝えします。
Before the show begins, there are a few requests we would like to make of the Soramame.
客席内でのモッシュ、ダイブ、ジャンプ等の危険行為は禁止となっております。
Dangerous acts such as moshing, diving, or jumping in the seating area are prohibited.
以上のことが守られない場合は、公演を一時中断、もしくは中止させていただく可能性がございます。
If these rules are not followed, the performance may be temporarily suspended or cancelled.
ペンライトは周りのお客様のご迷惑にならないよう、ご配慮お願いいたします。
Please be considerate of other guests when using penlights so as not to bother them.
頭の上に出したり、大きく左右に振り回すと、
Raising them above your head or swinging them widely from side to side
後ろのお客様や周りのお客様のご迷惑となる場合がございます。
may bother the guests behind you or around you.
スタッフが注意させていただく場合がございますので、ご了承ください。
Please note that staff members may approach you and ask you to stop.
本公演は映像配信および写真撮影用のカメラが会場内に入り、
Please be aware that cameras for video streaming and photography will be in the venue,
お客様の様子が映り込む場合がございます。
and you may be caught on camera.
これらの映像や写真はプロモーション等に使用される可能性がございますので、
Please note that these videos and photos may be used for promotional purposes,
あらかじめご了承ください。
so we ask for your understanding in advance.
客席内での携帯電話、スマートフォンの使用は禁止です。
The use of mobile phones and smartphones in the seating area is prohibited.
携帯電話や音の鳴る機械の電源はあらかじめお切りくださいますようお願い申し上げます。
We ask that you turn off the power to your mobile phones and any other devices that make noise beforehand.
また携帯電話、スマートフォン...
Also, mobile phones, smartphones...
のお客様による撮影、録音、録画は固くお断りします。
...recording, audio recording, and filming by the audience is strictly prohibited.
万が一発見した場合は、データ削除の上、退場していただく場合がございます。
If discovered, the data may be deleted and you may be asked to leave.
最後に、ライブの途中で具合が悪くなったりしたら、お近くのスタッフにお声がけください。
Lastly, if you feel unwell during the live, please inform the staff nearby.
また、地震、火事などの非常時は、
Also, in case of emergencies such as earthquakes or fires,
慌てずスタッフの誘導に従って避難していただきますようお願いいたします。
please do not panic and follow the staff's guidance to evacuate.
配信でご視聴のお客様へ、本ライブの録音、録画、
For those watching via the stream, recording, filming,
ミラー配信や違法アップロードは固くお断りします。
mirror distribution, and illegal uploads of this live are strictly prohibited.
その代わり、スクリーンショットを撮影して
Instead, you are more than welcome to take screenshots
画像とともにSNSに投稿していただくことは大歓迎です。
and post them on SNS along with the images.
本公演のハッシュタグは、#SorAZGravity となります。
The hashtag for this performance is #SorAZGravity.
それでは公演開始まで今しばらくお待ちください。
Please wait a little longer until the performance begins.
AZKi メジャーデビューEP 「3枚目の地図」 好評配信中！
AZKi Major Debut EP '3枚目の地図' Now Streaming!
「トウキョウ・シャンディ・ランデヴ」(Cover) 配信中！
'Tokyo Shandy Rendezvous' (Cover) Now Streaming!
「Sincerely」(Cover) 配信中！
'Sincerely' (Cover) Now Streaming!
みんな聞こえてるー？
Can everyone hear me?
聞こえてるー！ありがとー！
You can hear me! Thank you!
ありがとー！
Thank you!
恒例の影ナレでございます！
This is the customary pre-show announcement!
やったー！みんな、まだ疲れてないよねー？
Yay! Everyone, you're not tired yet, right?
始まってないから(笑)
It hasn't even started yet (laughs).
どうですか、夜…夜っていうほど夜でもないんだけど。
How is it? The evening... it's not quite late enough to call it 'evening' yet, but.
夜…ま、夜、夜公演ですよ。
Evening... well, it's the evening performance.
昼はいっぱい盛り上がったんで、昼公演をみんな越えられますよねー？
The afternoon performance was really exciting, so everyone can surpass that, right?
今初めて見るっていう人ももちろんいると思うんで。
I'm sure there are some people seeing it for the first time now, too.
そういう方たちも新鮮な気持ちで楽しんでもらえたら嬉しいなって思います。
I'd be happy if those people could enjoy it with a fresh feeling.
はい！分かりましたかー？
Okay! Did you understand?
ハッシュタグは #SorAZGravity でポストしてください！
Please post using the hashtag #SorAZGravity!
はい！そらとものみんな、仲良く楽しくライブを楽しんでください！
Okay! All the Soratomo, please enjoy the live together and have fun!
それじゃあちょっと待っててね。えらいぞー！
Well then, please wait a little. Good job!
はーい！待ってるー！
Okay! We're waiting!
踏み始めようぜ
Let's start stepping
僕らのFuturity
Our Futurity
見つめあう朝が来るまで
Until the morning we gaze at each other comes
響く 触れる 光る
Resonating, touching, shining,
君の声が
your voice
真っさらな頃
From a brand new place,
何億光年も 彼方の宇宙へ
millions of light years away, to the universe beyond
二重極の星じゃ
In a double-poled star,
描けなかったような 物語が生まれてる
a story that couldn't be drawn is being born
方程式に 導かれて
Guided by an equation,
この音が聞こえた時
when I heard this sound
今 君が感じてる心拍数
The heart rate you're feeling now
共鳴していく
is resonating
感情 友情 愛情 当たり前に抱ける奇跡
Emotion, friendship, affection, the miracle of holding them naturally
同じ世界で 巡り会えたのは 必然の未来
Meeting in the same world is an inevitable future
マグネット 手を振ればほら
Magnet, if we wave our hands, look,
繋がってるから 星座のように
we're connected like a constellation
マグネット またきっとどんな場所でも
Magnet, I'm sure in any place,
惹かれあう 運命のまま
we'll be attracted to each other, as destiny intended
真っさらな頃 何億通りで
From a brand new place, in billions of ways,
手探りの宇宙へ
into the searching universe
不完全だってさ 駆け出しのような
Even if incomplete, like just starting out,
誰も知らない夢を見る
dreaming a dream that nobody knows
予測不可能な 相互作用は
The unpredictable interaction is,
指と指 合わせた時
when our fingers touched
今 ここで混ざり合うシグナル
Now the signals are mixing here
「トウキョウ・シャンディ・ランデヴ」(Cover)
"Tokyo Shandy Rendezvous" (Cover)
...運命して見せる
...I'll show you it's destiny.
「Sincerely」(Cover)
"Sincerely" (Cover)
底も... 傷も... きっとも... 叶えたいと誓ったのに
Even the bottom... even the pain... surely... even though I swore I wanted it to come true...
2024年3月6日(水) Release Mini Album STAR STAR★T
Released on Wednesday, March 6, 2024: Mini Album "STAR STAR★T"
広い世界で　見つめ合った瞬間　確かに感じたんだ
In this wide world, the moment our eyes met, I certainly felt it.
歌ってみた「可愛くてごめん」
Song Cover: "Kawaikute Gomen"
探していた君が
It's you, the one I've been searching for.
2023.12.20 Release SorAZ メジャーデビューアルバム Futurity Step
Released on December 20, 2023: SorAZ Major Debut Album "Futurity Step"
Major Debut Live「First Gravity」 CD物販限定特典
Major Debut Live "First Gravity" CD Merchandise Exclusive Bonus
エルタマ 当日差し入れ企画 参加者様 一覧
Eltama Day-of Catering Project Participant List
振り切り出したこの靴が
These shoes that have started to shake off everything
響き出したあの音が
That sound that has started to resonate
今なら特別に輝いて
Now, it's shining especially bright
理屈はもういらないね
Logic is no longer needed
拘束も越えられる
Even constraints can be overcome
この目で見つめて何度でも
With these eyes, looking on again and again
マグネット またねと手を振ればほら
Magnet, if we wave our hands saying "see you again," look
繋がってるから星座のように
We're connected, like a constellation
マグネット またきっとどんな場所でも
Magnet, surely again, no matter where we are
惹かれあう定めの方へ
Towards the destiny that draws us together
そう、二人の声が
So, our two voices...
差し入れを贈ってくださったそらとも・開拓者の皆様、本当にありがとうございます！
To all Soratomo and Pioneers who sent catering, thank you very much!
言い続けた未来のためばかり
Always for the sake of the future I kept talking about
今という時間費やすけれど
Even though I spend the time that is "now"
降り積もっていく感情とここにいたら
If I'm here with these accumulating emotions
思いして弾けた心がもう一度動き出すよ
My heart that burst with thought will start moving once more
震えだした鼓動
My heartbeat has started to tremble
胸の痛みも涙もわけもすべて
The pain in my chest, the tears, the reasons, everything
強さに変えて
Turning it all into strength
飲み込んだ想い青い空に飛ばせ
Send those swallowed emotions into the blue sky
繋がらぬメロディ流れる星に変わってく
The disconnected melody turns into a shooting star
君のために歌うよ
I'll sing for your sake
君に届くようにと
So that it reaches you
輝きは世界中を越えて
The brilliance crosses the whole world
確かにここで重ねあった鼓動
The heartbeats we layered together here for certain
触れ合う音が光になって
The sounds touching each other turn into light
降り注ぐこの一瞬が
This moment pouring down
永遠なぞ
Like an eternity
煌めいては色づいてゆく君と描いた世界
It's sparkling and gaining color, the world I drew with you
いつだって明日は来るだなんて
Saying that tomorrow will always come
言って欲しくもない朝もあるけど
There are mornings I don't even want to hear that
宵闇に消えてもこのまま隠れられなくて
Even if I disappear in the dusk, I can't stay hidden like this
静寂を断ち切って叫びたい声を歌に変え
Cutting through the silence, I'll turn the voice that wants to shout into a song
いつもそこにある
It's always there
隔て阻む壁も壊して進め
Break down the walls that divide and obstruct us, and move forward
胸の奥にある
It's deep in my heart
忘れたフリで誤魔化し切れない傷も
Even the wounds I can't fully hide by pretending to forget
乗り越えてゆく
I will overcome them
絡まった想い音に変えて飛ばせ
Turn those tangled emotions into sound and send them flying
生まれるメロディ激しく鼓動奏で合う
The emerging melody and the intense heartbeat play together
言葉だけじゃ足りない
Words alone are not enough
歌じゃなくちゃ届かない
If it's not a song, it won't reach
情熱が胸を熱くさせて
Let passion make my chest feel hot
確かにここで分かりあえた鼓動
The heartbeats that understood each other here for certain
時の流れを逆らうように開かれた
Opened up as if defying the flow of time
何度だって歌うから君の場所が
I'll sing again and again so that your place
いつも光に包まれるように
Will always be wrapped in light
すべてが崩れ出しそうで
When everything seems about to crumble
どこにも歩き出せない時は
And I can't step out anywhere
送り続けるこの鼓動
I'll keep sending this heartbeat
聞こえる場所探し踏み出すよ
Searching for a place where it can be heard, I'll step out
遠くの星がささやくように
Like a distant star whispering...
2024年3月6日(水) Release Mini Album STAR STAR*T リリース決定！
March 6, 2024 (Wed) Release: Mini Album STAR STAR*T confirmed!
いつも何かを伝えるように歌ってる
I'm singing as if to always convey something
飲み込んだ思い 青い空に飛ばせ
Let the swallowed thoughts fly into the blue sky
歌ってみた『可愛くてごめん』 配信中！
Cover of 'Kawaii kute Gomen' now streaming!
繋がるメロディ 流れる星に変わってく
The connecting melody turns into a shooting star
SorAZ メジャーデビューアルバム Futurity Step 配信中！
SorAZ Major Debut Album 'Futurity Step' now streaming!
君のために歌うよ 君に届くようにと
I'll sing for you, so that it reaches you
SorAZ Major Debut Live "First Gravity" CD物販限定特典
Major Debut Live 'First Gravity' CD merchandise exclusive benefits
輝きは世界中を超えて
The radiance transcends the whole world
エルタマ お引出し差し入れ企画 参加者様一覧
List of participants in the Eruma gift delivery project
差し入れを贈ってくださったそらまめの皆様、本当にありがとうございます！
To all the Soramames who sent gifts, thank you so much!
確かにここで重ね合えた鼓動
The heartbeats that certainly overlapped here
触れ合う音が光になって降り注ぐ
The touching sounds turn into light and pour down
この一瞬が永遠だと
That this moment is eternal
煌めいては色づいていく
Sparkling and gaining color
AZKi メジャーデビュー EP『3枚目の地図』好評配信中！
AZKi Major Debut EP '3-maime no Chizu' now streaming!
君と描いた世界 君と描く
The world I drew with you, drawing with you
音が飛び立つ
The sounds take flight
AZKi『トウキョウ・シャンディ・ランデヴ』(Cover) 配信中！
AZKi 'Tokyo Shandy Rendezvous' (Cover) now streaming!
切なき心の窓
The window of my painful heart
AZKi『Sincerely』(Cover) 配信中！
AZKi 'Sincerely' (Cover) now streaming!
2024年3月6日(水) Release Mini Album STAR STAR*T リリース決定！
March 6, 2024 (Wed) Release: Mini Album STAR STAR*T confirmed!
いつも何かを伝えるように歌ってる
I'm singing as if to always convey something
飲み込んだ思い 青い空に飛ばせ
Let the swallowed thoughts fly into the blue sky
歌ってみた『可愛くてごめん』 配信中！
Cover of 'Kawaii kute Gomen' now streaming!
愛しさよ
Oh, my dear
切なさは
The sadness is
抱えたままで
Still being held
辿り着く音 確かなメロディ
The sound I reached, a certain melody
これは生きた証だから
Because this is proof of having lived
今も聞こえている
I can still hear it now
聞こえてるよ
I can hear it
二人だけの歌だよ
It's a song just for the two of us
不意に 向こう側の気配
Suddenly, a presence from the other side
きっと目に映そう
I'll surely reflect it in my eyes
お待たせ ついてきて
Sorry to keep you waiting, follow me
言葉積み重ねよう
Let's pile up the words
高すぎる壁さえも 飛んでしまおう
Let's fly over even walls that are too high
通り抜けたって 何も楽しくないって
Passing through isn't fun at all
ネバーイナフ 君が教えてくれていたんだ
"Never enough," you were teaching me
腕をサンザン 駆け合わせ
Intertwining our arms so many times
時々 相当 間違って
Sometimes making quite a few mistakes
それもラララ 気にせずに 何度でも挑もう
Without worrying about those, la la la, let's try again and again
だって I know myself
Because I know myself
意味のない評価で 世界比べないで
Don't compare the world with meaningless evaluations
叶えたい本音は 全てを包み込む太陽
The true feelings I want to fulfill are like the sun that envelops everything
いっそ 好き放題 上を目指して
Might as well aim for the top as much as I want
立ちはだかる壁を登って
Climbing up the wall that stands in the way
刻んでいきたいな そして次に望む
I want to carve it in, and then hope for the next
越えたいあの未来
That future I want to surpass
想像したら 鼓動が聞こえたんだ
When I imagined it, I heard my heartbeat
作り込んだ道なんて 全部したがわずに
Without following all the pre-made paths
響く音のまま 心が赴くまま
Just as the sound resonates, just as the heart leads
ずっと君なら 君なら 一緒に何でも
If it's always you, if it's you, we can do anything together
築ける
Build
躓いて 光が何も見えなくなっても
Even if I stumble and can't see any light at all
振り向いたら笑える こんな場所がある
If I look back, there's a place where I can smile
腕をサンザン 駆け合わせ
Intertwining our arms so many times
時々 相当 間違って それもラララ
Sometimes making quite a few mistakes, and that too, la la la
気にせずに 何度でも挑もう
Without worrying, let's try again and again
いつも be yourself
Always be yourself
ためらわないで ほら 何も始まらない
Don't hesitate, see, nothing will start
些細な勇気で 明日を変えるまでも
Until even a tiny bit of courage changes tomorrow
意味のない評価で 世界比べないで
Don't compare the world with meaningless evaluations
叶えたい本音は 全てを包み込む太陽
The true feelings I want to fulfill are like the sun that envelops everything
いっそ 好き放題 上を目指して
Might as well aim for the top as much as I want
立ちはだかる壁を登って
Climbing up the wall that stands in the way
刻んでいきたいな そして次に望む
I want to carve it in, and then hope for the next
越えたいあの未来
That future I want to surpass
挑め このダイナミックな未来
Challenge this dynamic future
せーの！
Ready, set...
せーので...
深呼吸...
...take a deep breath.
始まっていく ここから
It's all starting from here.
ready go!
みんな、来てくれてありがとう！
Everyone, thank you for coming!
楽しもうねー！
Let's have fun!
大気圏突き抜けて
Breaking through the atmosphere,
イメージも歌声も
both my image and my singing voice...
意識を飛び越えて響く
...resonate beyond consciousness.
kira kira
Sparkling
天体も星雲も
The celestial bodies and nebulae,
漂い巡り会い
drifting and meeting by chance,
瞬間、ドキする奇跡だね
the moment, it's a heart-pounding miracle.
groovy
火照るように高まって
Heating up and rising,
クルクル回るみんな
everyone is spinning around.
まるで...
Just like...
...ミラーボール
...a mirror ball.
私たちの夢の First Gravity
The First Gravity of our dreams.
思い切り遊ぼう！
Let's play with all our might!
ETERNITY 宙を駆けて
ETERNITY, racing through space,
振り切っちゃって飛ぼう
shaking it off and taking flight.
加速する鼓動を生み出す光
The light that creates a racing heartbeat,
今ここで繋がった
we've connected right here and now.
照らして 照らし合って
Illuminate and light each other up.
せーので！
Ready, set...
頷いて！
Nod!
始まっていく Wonder
The Wonder is beginning.
ready go!
みんな！ 次行っちゃうよ！
Everyone! Moving on to the next one!
ときめきタップして
Tapping into excitement,
拓くわ新時代
we'll open up a new era.
可能性その身はなんて
How boundless is that possibility...
amazing
次世代のエーテルに
To the ether of the next generation,
ドキドキ伝播する
sending out heart-pounding ripples.
解釈一致でしょう 生きるって
It's a shared interpretation, right? That living is...
fantastic
運命のシンコペーション
A syncopation of destiny,
星屑のアウェイから
from a stardust getaway.
投げる...
Throwing...
...きらびやか
...a brilliant glare.
満ち溢れ輝く future sign
The Future Sign brimming with radiance.
キャッチして glorious
Catch it, GLORIOUS!
アイという 奏でるのは
What we play is the sound of love...
ミラクルでいい
...and it can be a miracle.
以心伝心でまるでテレパス
Telepathic, like hearts beating as one,
今という瞬間を
taking in the moment called 'now'.
感じて 感じ合って
Feel it, feel each other's hearts.
せーので！
Ready, set...
深呼吸！
Take a deep breath!
見たことない wonder
A Wonder you've never seen before,
君と...
with you...
...ずっと
...forever.
思いと思いが
Thoughts and feelings...
作る世界 ここにある
...create the world that's right here.
...ここにいるよ
...I'm here
歌えば
If we sing
ひとつになれる もっと
We can become one, even more
なれるよ
We can be
自由に
Free
ようこそ ここは バイアスのない
Welcome, this is a bias-free
二人のエキスポ Gonna be spacey
Expo of the two of us, gonna be spacey
私たちの夢のファーストブレス
Our dream's first breath
思いきり遊ぼう
Let's play with all our might
AZ... 空を駆けて
AZ... soaring through the sky
振り切って ジャンピングゴー
Shaking it off, jumping go
高くハンズアップで呼び出す光
Calling out the light with hands up high
今ここで繋がった
We've connected right here and now
照らして
Shine upon us
照らし合って
Shine on each other
せーのっで
On the count of three
深呼吸
Deep breath
どこまでも行こうよ
Let's go wherever we want
せーのっで
Ready, set...
頷いて
Nod our heads
始まっていく ワンダー レディ ゴー
It's beginning, wonder ready go
やる声もみんなで盛り上がっていきましょう！
Let's all get excited with our voices too!
2曲目もいくよー！
Here comes the second song too!
スタート向こう側の気配 きっと目に映そう
A sign from the other side of the start, surely we'll see it
誤魔化さないで
Don't play tricks
言葉積み重ねよう
Let's stack our words
高すぎた壁さえも
Even the walls that were too high
飛んでしまうから
We'll just fly over them
通り抜けたって
Even if we pass through
何も楽しくないって
There's no fun in it
Never Know
君が教えてくれていたんだ
You were the one who taught me that
夢を散々掛け合わせ
Multiplying dreams over and over
時に散々間違って
Sometimes making many mistakes
それもラフ・ラフ 気にせずに
Keep it rough-rough, and don't worry about it
何度でも挑もう
Let's try again and again
だって
Because
I know myself
意味のない評価で世界比べないで
Don't compare the world with meaningless evaluations
叶えたい本音は
My true feelings I want to fulfill
すべてを包み込む太陽
Are the sun that envelops everything
いっそ好き放題 上を目指して
Might as well aim for the top as much as I want
立ちはだかる壁を登って
Climbing the walls that stand in my way
刻んでいきたいな
I want to carve it in
そして次に望む
And then, looking forward to the next
越えたい あの未来
That future I want to surpass
そっとしたら
When I did it softly
鼓動が聞こえたんだ
I heard the heartbeat
作り込んだ道なんて
A path that was artificially made
全速力で ぶち壊し行こう
Let's smash it at full speed
響く音のまま
Just like the sounds that echo
心が赴くまま
Just as the heart dictates
ずっと 君なら 君なら
Always, if it's you, if it's you
一緒に 何でも 築ける
We can build anything together
つまずいて 視界が
Tripping up, my vision
何も見えなくなっても
Even if I can't see anything anymore
振り向いたら 笑える
If I turn around, I can laugh
そんな場所がある
There's such a place
夢を散々掛け合わせ
Multiplying dreams over and over
時に散々間違って
Sometimes making many mistakes
それもラフ・ラフ 気にせずに
Keep it rough-rough, and don't worry about it
何度でも挑もう
Let's try again and again
いつも
Always
Be yourself
試さないと ほら
See, unless you try
何も始まらない
Nothing will ever start
些細な勇気で
With just a little bit of courage
明日を変えるまで もっと
Until it changes tomorrow, even more
意味のない評価で世界比べないで
Don't compare the world with meaningless evaluations
叶えたい本音は
My true feelings I want to fulfill
すべてを包み込む太陽
Are the sun that envelops everything
いっそ好き放題 上を目指して
Might as well aim for the top as much as I want
立ちはだかる壁を登って
Climbing the walls that stand in my way
刻んでいきたいな
I want to carve it in
そして次に望む
And then, looking forward to the next
越えたい あの未来
That future I want to surpass
抱こう そう 大事な未来
Let's embrace it, that important future
NOVAは必然
A nova is inevitable
君も気づいてるのかな
I wonder if you've noticed too
遥か宇宙から見た僕らは
Looking from deep space, we are...
まるでちっぽけな星屑
...just like tiny stardust.
君と出会えた瞬間に
At the moment I met you,
僕ら星座になれたの
we were able to become a constellation.
時間(とき)を越えて Non-Stop 未来へ
Transcending time, non-stop to the future,
二つ重なって超絶ミラクル
the two overlapping are a transcendent miracle.
誰も止められない魔法
A magic that no one can stop,
レベチな僕らの銀河パーティーナイト
our next-level galaxy party night.
Wow Wow 二人は Destiny
Wow, wow, we are destiny.
引力に惹かれ光る COMEDY
A comedy shining, pulled by gravity.
ドキドキして愛して
Heart pounding, love me,
ワクワクして二人のグラビティ
feeling excited, our gravity.
感情のままに So Dance Music
Let the emotions flow, so dance music.
擦れ違いも待って狂い
Even misunderstandings, wait and go crazy,
始めようぜ僕らの Gravity
let's start our gravity.
見つめてて 朝が来るまで Yeah!
Keep watching until morning comes, yeah!
これが完全無欠なイリュージョン
This is a flawless illusion,
まさに完璧なフュージョン
truly a perfect fusion.
歌い踊ればソリューション
Singing and dancing is the solution,
ここは僕たちのリージョン
this is our region.
みんなの力が重なり広がる
Everyone's power overlaps and spreads out,
たった一つのユニバース
to a single universe.
ねえ ちょっと泣いたって
Hey, even if you cry a little,
明日は晴れる Take it easy
tomorrow will be sunny, so take it easy.
一人でいないで Hold on
Don't be alone, hold on,
つながるいつでも未来で Let me out
connecting anytime in the future, let me out.
Wow Wow 二人のシンパシー
Wow, wow, our sympathy.
求め合う鼓動が今 Bumping
Our seeking heartbeats are bumping now,
見逃さないで 感じて
don't miss it, feel it,
悟り込みになって これぞインフィニティ
get enlightened, this is infinity.
考える前に Just doing
Just doing it before thinking,
自分でも怖い声で
with a voice that's scary even to myself.
これからが僕らの Gravity
From now on, it's our gravity,
ついてきて たどり着くまで Yeah!
follow us until we reach it, yeah!
何回でも星座を作るよ
I'll create constellations over and over again.
二人で Six-bundle of stars
The two of us, a six-bundle of stars.
描いてた未来へ
Towards the future we envisioned.
Wow Wow 二人は Destiny
Wow, wow, we are destiny.
強くなる絆はまだ Growing
The bond that grows stronger is still growing.
ドキドキして愛して
Heart pounding, love me,
ワクワクして二人のグラビティ
feeling excited, our gravity.
間違いだらけでも Oh my
Even if it's full of mistakes, oh my,
凄まじくてもまた狂い
even if it's terrifying, going crazy again,
始めようぜ僕らの Gravity
let's start our gravity.
見つめてて 朝が来るまで Yeah!
Keep watching until morning comes, yeah!
First Gravity
そらとものみんなー！
Everyone, Soratomo!
こんそらー！
Konsora!
こんあずきー！
Kon-Azuki!
二人合わせて、せーの、SorAZです！
Together, one, two, we are SorAZ!
みんなありがとう。ということで、SorAZ Major Debut Live『First Gravity』at CLUB CITTA' 夜公演にお越しいただきありがとうございます。
Thank you, everyone. And so, thank you for coming to the SorAZ Major Debut Live "First Gravity" at CLUB CITTA' evening performance.
みんな盛り上がってますかー？
Is everyone pumped up?
全力で楽しんでますかー？
Are you enjoying yourselves to the fullest?
全方位見えてるよー。
I can see everyone in every direction.
コメントも見えてるよー。
I can see the comments too.
あ、配信のみんなも見えてるよー。ありがとう。
Ah, I can see everyone on the stream too. Thank you.
いやー、夜公演だよ。夜公演やってきましたね。
Wow, it's the evening performance. The evening performance has finally arrived.
夕方だー。
It's evening.
夕方だ。でもだんだん日が暮れていくから夜公演だ。はい。
It's evening. But the sun will gradually set, so it's the evening performance. Yes.
あ、お水おいしいタイム。
Ah, it's the 'water is delicious' time.
おいしかった。おいしかった。
It was delicious. It was delicious.
またみんなの力で甘くなったわ。ありがとう。
It's become sweet again thanks to everyone's power. Thank you.
みんなの力でそらちゃんの水が甘くなっておりますが。
So Sora-chan's water is becoming sweet thanks to everyone's power...
ということで、そういえば、じゃあちょっと聞きたいことがあるんですけど。
Anyway, that reminds me, there's something I want to ask.
みんな、昼公演に...
Did everyone... the afternoon performance...
…てくれたよっていう人いますかー？
...anyone here who came [to the afternoon show]?
ありがとうございます！
Thank you very much!
今回が初めてだよっていう人ー！
Anyone here for whom this is your first time?
おーい！ありがとう！
Wow! Thank you!
じゃあ、昼公演、配信で見たよっていう人？
Then, anyone who watched the afternoon show on the stream?
あ、配信見て来てくれた人もいると思いますね。
Ah, I think there are people who watched the stream and then came here.
ありがとうございます。
Thank you very much.
というわけで…
And so...
恒例のお知らせあります。
We have the usual announcement.
現在、YouTubeでご覧の皆様。
To everyone watching on YouTube right now.
えー、ここまでが無料配信となります！
Well, this concludes the free portion of the stream!
あー、まだ来たばかり…
Ah, we just started...
まだ来たばかり。
We just started.
ま、オープニングありまして、「せーので！」「スケオト」「ふたりディスティニー」とやってきましたが…
Well, we had the opening, performed "Se-no de!", "Sukeoto", and "Futari Destiny"...
はい、無料配信はここまでということで…
Yes, the free stream ends here...
続きはぜひ配信チケット、ぽちっとな。
For the rest, please click and get a streaming ticket.
ぽちっとな。
Click.
ここにあるよ、ここに。
It's right here, right here.
ここにありますので、ぜひぜひこの後続きも見ていてくださると嬉しいです。よろしくお願いします！
It's right here, so we'd be very happy if you'd continue watching after this. Thank you!
お願いー！
Please!
いやー、はい。というわけで。
Well, yes. And so.
なんだっけね。
What was it again?
冒頭無料はこちらで終了です。
The free preview ends here.
本編続きをご視聴されたい方は、チケットぴあにてご購入お願いします。
If you wish to watch the rest of the performance, please purchase a ticket on Ticket Pia.